David W. Schremser

1725 Lakecliffe Drive, Unit C.

Wheaton, IL. 60189

(630) 485-1194

DSchremser@gmail.com

Job Skills

I am a reliable, organized and enthusiastic worker. A quick learner with excellent communication and problem solving skills, I have the ability to adapt to any given situation. I have several successful years in customer service along with experience in Microsoft Office, Excel, POS System and Intuit QuickBase.

Professional Experience

Certified Warranties Corporation

- Account Manager May 2014--Present
- Manage accounts, track payments, and monitor sales
- Track new sales opportunities and develop new sales leads
- Make difficult decisions regarding payments or employee progress
- Monitor employee progress and development
- Issue payments to vendors, clients, or third parties as required
- Demonstrate new ideas, develop projects, and lead a team
- Lead by example
- Plan, oversee development, and completion of complex projects

Gallagher Bassett Services, Inc. – Third Party Administrator-McDonald's

- Claim Representative April 2013 May 2014
- Determine liability in complex situations involving many variables.
- Assess damages related to losses and issue payments accordingly.
- Review, and summarize documentation including medical records and other property estimates.
- Organize the facts of a given incident and use the information to make difficult decisions.
- Negotiating settlement agreements with claimants and attorneys.

Costco Wholesale – Customer Service

- Morning Merchandise Hardlines Stocker March 2013 April 2013
- Morning Merchandise Produce Stocker July 2012 March 2013
- Food Service Employee July 2010-July 2012

Buffalo Wild Wings – Server – January 2009 – June 2006

- Training new hires at new locations to ensure knowledge of computer system & products.
- Customer service and product knowledge.

Education

Bachelor Degree - Northern Illinois University - Spring 2011 - Fall 2009

Associate Degree – Elgin Community College - Spring 2009 – Fall 2006

High School Diploma – St. Edward Central Catholic High School – 2006- 2002

<u>Hobbies</u> – Football, Music, Frisbee Golf, Camping, and Hiking.